internetadvices.com 2013-08-06

# Privacy Policy | Internet Advices Statistical Information About Web

We take your privacy seriously. Please take a moment to read this privacy policy. 

**Register :**

When you register to use forums or other Services, we ask you to provide certain information, which may include your email address, home address, birth year, gender, health conditions, credit card number and zip code, as well as a password for your account. We will not provide Advertisers or Partners to this personal information without your permission.

**Device Information :**

We may collect information about the browser, computer, mobile phone, smartphone or other device you use to access the Services to measure the effectiveness of those Services.

**Geolocation Data :**

For certain mobile applications we offer, we may (or may enable a third party, including an advertiser) request your geolocation information in order to provide you with ads, offers, search or other functionality. If you agree to such collection, we (or the third party) will maintain information regarding your geolocation and may use it to help enable that functionality, or other functionality we describe to you in a privacy notice provided with the mobile application.

**IP Addresses :**

We log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our Web sites and mobile applications.

**Google Adsense :**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

**We respect your privacy** :

The information you, and/or your browser submit to our website will never be sold or rent to anyone.

The web server automatically collects website logs on whoever visits the site. Those logs are not personally identifiable and we will not sell or rent them to anyone.

**Use of cookies :**

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service. Cookies are used only for tracking visitors from where they have arrived on the site, their time spent on the site, how the user navigated the site and other visitor related information including but not limited to what kind of browser. Cookies are also used for storing user preferences. Cookies and cookie information are not personally identifiable and we will not sell or rent them to anyone.

**Google Analytics :**

Third party Google Analytics may use cookies for above mentioned purposes. Cookies are NOT used for anything else.

**DoubleClick DART :**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

**Other Important Information :**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Best Regards.  
** **Internet Advices Developer Team**
